<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hiep Tran</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hiep Tran</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:53:05 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I Started Writing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-started-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:53:05 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-started-writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we can use an AI to generate an essay from our ideas. It will take me a few minutes to review and publish my essay instead of spending hours, or days to finish my writing. Using AI will save my time and my effort. I just need an idea, AI will do everything else. It is easy but why I start writing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, writing is thinking. To write well I have to think clearly. Thinking clearly is hard, I must truly understand my thoughts. Why did I have those thoughts? How to connect the things from my thoughts. It will help me consolidate my knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 23:14:17 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my sites! I’m Hiep Tran, and I’m excited to share my journey in the world of software engineering and technology with you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I’ll be posting about:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Learning Journey&lt;/strong&gt;: Sharing the resources, tips, and experiences that have shaped my skills and knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Updates on the projects I’m working on, including challenges faced and solutions found.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thoughts on Minimalism&lt;/strong&gt;: Exploring how a minimalist approach influences my coding style and life in general.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-hello-world&#34;&gt;Why &amp;ldquo;Hello, World!&amp;rdquo;?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The phrase “Hello, World!” is often the first program written by newcomers to programming. It’s a simple way to demonstrate the basics of syntax and the joy of creating something from scratch. Just like that first program, this blog represents a starting point for my exploration of the tech world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
